{
  "session_id": "39_Steve",
  "profile": {
    "id": "39_Steve",
    "name": "Steve",
    "age": 75,
    "role": "Zookeeper",
    "timeline": [
      {
        "stage": "Youth",
        "topic": "Night shift with lions",
        "context": "Respect for nature."
      },
      {
        "stage": "Adulthood",
        "topic": "The animal escape",
        "context": "Crisis."
      },
      {
        "stage": "Old Age",
        "topic": "Retirement volunteering",
        "context": "Can't stay away."
      }
    ]
  },
  "extracted_knowledge": [
    {
      "turn_id": 2,
      "original_text": "Working the night shift at the zoo, especially with the lions, was a unique experience.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " night shift",
          "type": "EVENT",
          "confidence": "0.9961"
        },
        {
          "text": " zoo",
          "type": "LOCATION",
          "confidence": "0.9966"
        },
        {
          "text": " lions",
          "type": "PERSON",
          "confidence": "0.9990"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 4,
      "original_text": "I remember this one night, there was a sudden power outage.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " power outage",
          "type": "EVENT",
          "confidence": "0.9987"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 6,
      "original_text": "It was during one of those unexpected thunderstorms.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " thunderstorms",
          "type": "EVENT",
          "confidence": "0.9987"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 6,
      "original_text": "The storm knocked out the power again, and this time, one of the lions managed to push open the gate of its enclosure.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " gate",
          "type": "ARTIFACT",
          "confidence": "0.9988"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 8,
      "original_text": "I became more vigilant and more committed to ensuring that both the animals and the staff were kept safe.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " staff",
          "type": "PERSON",
          "confidence": "0.9992"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 10,
      "original_text": "After that incident, I took on more responsibilities in training new staff and developing better protocols for emergencies.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " protocols",
          "type": "ARTIFACT",
          "confidence": "0.9990"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 10,
      "original_text": "I also became more involved in conservation efforts, realizing how crucial our work was, not just for the animals in our care but for their wild counterparts as well.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " wild counterparts",
          "type": "PERSON",
          "confidence": "0.9994"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 16,
      "original_text": "Another challenge was ensuring that we had the resources to implement these changes.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " resources",
          "type": "ARTIFACT",
          "confidence": "0.9993"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 16,
      "original_text": "We had to work with the management to secure funding and support for new training programs and equipment.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " management",
          "type": "PERSON",
          "confidence": "0.9993"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 18,
      "original_text": "I started collaborating with local conservation groups and became involved in a program aimed at protecting habitats of wild lions.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " conservation groups",
          "type": "ORGANIZATION",
          "confidence": "0.9977"
        },
        {
          "text": " wild lions",
          "type": "PERSON",
          "confidence": "0.9994"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 20,
      "original_text": "I started volunteering at a local wildlife rescue and rehabilitation center.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " wildlife rescue",
          "type": "ORGANIZATION",
          "confidence": "0.9965"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 20,
      "original_text": "Plus, I help run educational programs for kids, teaching them about animal conservation and the importance of protecting our natural world.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " kids",
          "type": "PERSON",
          "confidence": "0.9990"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 20,
      "original_text": "It feels like I’m passing the torch to the next generation, and that's incredibly fulfilling.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " next generation",
          "type": "PERSON",
          "confidence": "0.9992"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "turn_id": 26,
      "original_text": "Another memory is the bond I formed with a young lion cub that was rejected by its mother.",
      "predicted_entities": [
        {
          "text": " lion cub",
          "type": "PERSON",
          "confidence": "0.9993"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}